So now let's see how we can evaluate a model automatically.
So this is a deeper type of evaluation,
but on the left hand side,
you can go under assessment and deployment and find model evaluation.
So as you can see, we have three kinds of evaluation.
We have the automatic evaluation to evaluate a model
against recommended metrics and it's going to be fully automated
as we've seen in diagram in the previous lecture.
But we also have humans.
You can bring your own work team and then humans are going to
give you feedback and evaluate up to two miles at a time.
And then you can also get humans,
but this time they can be an AWS managed work team.
So different kind of evaluations,
but I just want to show you the flow on how to create one
just so you can get a better idea.
So let's go for automatic and I'll call this one demo evaluation.
We're not going to run one, we just want to look at the options.
But we need to select a model.
For example, let's evaluate Amazon,
Titan to text G1 Express.
And next we need to choose what is the type of the model
evaluation task that we're going to evaluate again.
So do we want to understand if it's good at general text
generation or if it's good at text summarization or question
and answer or text classification?
As you can see, you don't have any custom type of text type,
just the ones are built in.
So let's say we want to evaluate for general text generation.
And then what do we want to evaluate for?
So some metrics, so for example, we can have a look at toxicity
to see if the model will generate harmful, offensive,
or inappropriate content.
So here we need to choose a prompt that I set to evaluate this metric.
So you can either use an available built in data sets.
And there's like the real toxicity prompts or the bold one,
which will give some challenges to the AI.
And we can have a look at the result of this evaluation.
Or we can use our own prompt data sets.
And again, it needs to be an Amazon S3.
And then here we have more option because we can test
against specific use cases of our business.
So each either option are fine based on what you're trying to do.
And also you can have other metrics such as accuracy.
So is it good about factual knowledge for the real world?
And robustness.
And again, for each of these tests,
you have some available data sets or you can build your own.
OK.
And then where do you want to store the evaluation results?
Again, in Amazon S3.
To perform this, you need an IM roll again
to write to your Amazon S3 bucket.
This can be automated right here.
And then you click on Create.
And it would actually do a model evaluation.
Now we don't do it because, well,
this is going to cost us a lot of money
because we're going to run the JNAI prompts
and then look at their outcome.
So obviously there's a certain cost associated with it.
But here we get some intention of how the model evaluation work.
And you can explore on your own text summarization,
question and answer, classification, and so on.
Where, again, built in data sets are provided for you,
which is super nice.
And we want to have humans.
We can create a human-based evaluation.
So by humans.
And here, the evaluation of all lower case.
And here, we select again a model, so whichever you want.
And then what is the task type?
So you have the same as before, but also
now you can create a custom task type.
And this is for your team to use and to perform a specific task.
Here, again, you would have some metrics
that can be suggested.
Or you can create your own metric if you want to.
So you have a bit more control because now you have humans
and humans can do whatever you want.
So again, you select this.
You select a rating method.
Do you want humans to evaluate based on the thumb up or down
or to write the answers on a five star method?
And you can have multiple metrics if you want it to.
And on top of it, you can add another model to compare
between two models if you want it to, for example, these two.
So a lot more customization is available for human-based
evaluation, but the ID remains the same.
So that's it for FM evaluation.
I hope you liked it.
And I will see you in the next lecture.